Stephen Trudell

steviejtrudell@gmail.com

Austin, TX 78749

(737) 402-0876

About

Full stack web developer leveraging over a decade of experience in audio engineering to provide creative solutions in website development and design. Recently earning a certificate from the Code Bootcamp at UT Austin, specializing in JavaScript and the MERN stack, Stephen is ready to offer excellent time management, work ethic, and attention to detail to a wide range of professional projects. Being flexible, reliable, quick to adapt, and known by colleagues as friendly and easy to work with in both large and small scale teams, as well as highly responsible and productive when working independently, Stephen is excited to apply his experience and passion in the diverse field of web development.

Skills

Certification 9

Full Stack Web Development

The University of Texas at Austin - 2022

Client Side	Technologies
JavaScript	PWAs
React	SPAs
CSS	Swipe
Bootstrap	Jest
Mobile Responsive	Git
HTML	Heroku
Server Side	DevOps
Server Side Node	<u>DevOps</u> MERN Stack
Node	MERN Stack
Node Express	MERN Stack AGILE
Node Express GraphQL	MERN Stack AGILE MVC

Experience

2010 - Present

Audio Engineer / Musician / Producer Various - Austin, TX

- Recording, mixing, mastering, and producing audio with DAW software, including Pro Tools, Ableton Live, Print Music, and various processing plug-ins.
- Working in chaotic and radid fire production/performance settings, both in the studio and on stage.
- Intuition in finding creative solutions to unrehearsed problems.
- Collaborating with a wide spectrum of colorful humans: as composers, band mates, crew mates, clients, and audiences.

2013 - Present

Cashier / Food Prep / Driver
The Soup Peddler - Austin, TX

- Self-sufficiency and a strong work ethic developed in a small workforce within a small company.
- Administering customer service skills and time management techniques in a restaurant environment.

2006 - 2013

Cashier

H-E-B Groceries - Bee Cave, TX

 Customer service and team work skills developed in a large workforce within a large company.

Education

A.A. In Foreign Language: French Austin Community College - 2013

- **PORTFOLIO** ► https://strudelandcoffee.github.io/react-portfolio
 - https://github.com/strudelAndCoffee
 - https://www.linkedin.com/in/stevie-trudell-atx

References

Available upon request.